Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art rental records, 1961-1973 COR0003.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Rental and sales, 1962-1981; Series 3
  - Rental gallery exhibitions and sales, 1962-1973; Series 3 Subseries 6
    - Liberman Print Sales, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 18)
    - Longo Print Sales, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 19)
    - John McLaughlin Exhibition Sales, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 20)
    - Peruvian Exhibition: Sales, 1966; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 21)
    - Photography Show, 1972 December; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 22)
    - Ponce de Leon-Sales, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 23)
    - Shalom of Safed Show, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 24)
    - Ronald Stark Show, 1973 December; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 25)
    - Sweden Exhibition Sales, 1967; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 26)
    - Thomas, Alma, 1972; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 27)
    - Unframed Print Show and Sale, 1971 November; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 28)
    - Washington Art Series: Sales and Catalogs, 1965; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 29)
    - Washington Art Series: Sales and Catalogs, 1964; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 30)
    - Washington Art Series: Sales and Catalogs, 1963; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 31)
    - Washington Art Series: Sales and Catalogs, 1962; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 32)
    - White, Joe, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 33)
    - Art Rental Wiley Show, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 34)
    - Woehrman, Ralph, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 35)
    - Woman's Show, 1972 April; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 36)
    - Woffard, Philip, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 6 (Box RG3.1-1998.006, Folder 37)